<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en-US">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content=""Maximize tranquility with our soundproof underlay – the ultimate solution for reducing noise and enhancing comfort in any space."Enhance your laminate floors with acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and comfort. Perfect for quieter, cozier living spaces.Enhance your laminate floors with acoustic underlay for improved soundproofing and comfort. Perfect for a quieter, more serene living space."Enhance your laminate flooring with acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and comfort. Perfect for quieter, cozier living spaces."Discover the top acoustic underlays for laminate flooring to enhance sound insulation and comfort in your home.Maximize your floor's soundproofing with our high-quality laminate acoustic underlay—ideal for reducing noise and enhancing comfort.Discover top-rated acoustic underlays for laminate flooring—enhance comfort and reduce noise with the best picks for your home.Yes, underlay is essential for laminate flooring to ensure stability, noise reduction, and comfort.Maximize your laminate flooring's comfort and soundproofing with high-quality acoustic underlay—enhanced stability and noise reduction for any space.Maximize your engineered flooring's comfort and soundproofing with premium acoustic underlay. Enhanced durability, improved acoustics."Enhance your laminate flooring with our acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and walking comfort. Perfect for a quieter home."Maximize floor sound insulation with Buildtec acoustic underlay—enhancing comfort and noise reduction in any space."Enhance your space with UK's top soundproof underlay for laminate flooring – enjoy peace and quiet in style!"Discover the UK's top soundproof underlays for laminate floors - enhance comfort & reduce noise with our expert picks!Discover the optimal underlay thickness for laminate flooring to ensure durability, comfort, and sound insulation. Get the best flooring support tips now!Discover the top acoustic underlays for vinyl flooring – enhance comfort, improve sound insulation, and prolong floor life with our expert picks.Enhance your vinyl floors with acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and comfort. Perfect for a quieter, more serene home environment.Enhance your floors with vinyl acoustic underlay for superior soundproofing and improved comfort. Perfect for a quieter, more serene living space.Enhance your wood flooring with our premium acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and walking comfort. Perfect for a peaceful home environment.Enhance your wooden floors with premium acoustic underlay for superior sound dampening and comfort. Perfect for peaceful living spaces.Maximize your laminate flooring's comfort and sound insulation with our premium 3mm acoustic underlay – the perfect foundation for a serene home.Choose the right underlay thickness for laminate flooring to ensure durability and comfort—usually between 1mm and 3mm."Discover the quietest underlayment options for laminate floors, ensuring a silent and comfortable living space.""Enhance your floors with our 3mm acoustic underlay – the perfect solution for superior sound insulation and comfort in any space.""Enhance your laminate flooring with our 4mm underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and durability. Perfect fit for a seamless finish.""Enhance your flooring with 5mm acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and comfort in every step.""High-quality 5mm underlay for enhanced comfort and durability beneath your laminate flooring. Perfect support and sound reduction.""Enhance your floors with 6mm acoustic underlay for superior soundproofing and improved comfort in any space. Perfect for noise reduction.""Enhance your laminate flooring with 6mm underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and noise reduction. Perfect support for a sturdy floor.""Enhance your flooring with our 6mm laminate underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and longevity. Perfect support for a flawless finish.""Enhance your laminate flooring with our durable 7mm underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and longevity. Perfect support for a flawless finish.""Enhance your laminate flooring with 8mm underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and durability. Perfect support for a flawless finish."Maximize your peace with our soundproof underlay for laminate flooring – the ultimate noise-reducing solution for serene living spaces."Enhance your space with soundproofing underlay for vinyl floors – the perfect solution for noise reduction and added comfort in any room."Discover if laminate flooring cuts down on noise in your home. Get the facts on its sound-dampening properties here."Enhance your wooden floors with premium soundproofing underlay. Reduce noise, increase comfort. Ideal for peaceful living spaces.""Maximize your floor's noise reduction with our premium soundproof wood floor underlay—quiet, durable, and easy to install."Discover the top soundproof underlays for wood floors – enhance comfort and reduce noise effectively in your space!"Discover top soundproofing underlayments for hardwood floors – enhance comfort and reduce noise in any space with our expert picks!""Explore methods to soundproof wooden floors effectively, enhancing comfort and reducing noise in your living space."Learn effective techniques to soundproof wooden floors using insulation, mats, and sealants for a quieter living space.Learn how to effectively soundproof beneath floorboards for a quieter home environment."Learn quick tips to soundproof under hardwood floors, reducing noise with effective insulation solutions for a quieter home."Discover the top soundproofing materials for floors to reduce noise and enhance tranquility in your space. Get effective solutions for peaceful living!"Enhance your wood flooring with our soundproof underlay for a quieter, more comfortable living space. Perfect for noise reduction and added insulation.""Enhance your solid wood flooring with premium acoustic underlay for improved sound reduction and comfort. Perfect for a peaceful home environment."Discover the top soundproofing underlays for noise reduction & comfort in your home or workspace. Find your ideal acoustic solution today!Maximize comfort and stability with our 6mm underlay, perfect for engineered wood flooring. Enhanced support and noise reduction."Explore the effectiveness of acoustic underlay in reducing noise and enhancing sound insulation in your living space."Discover if acoustic underlay enhances your space's soundproofing and comfort—worth the investment for peace and tranquility at home or work.Discover whether underlay is necessary for your wood flooring installation to enhance durability and comfort.Maximize floor sound insulation with acoustic underlay—effective noise reduction for peaceful living spaces. Enjoy serene home acoustics!Explore top-rated acoustic underlay options for timber floors: enhance comfort, reduce noise, and improve longevity. Perfect for any home or office!"Explore the impact of acoustic underlay on sound insulation and flooring performance. Enhance your space with effective noise reduction solutions.""Discover top acoustic underlays for engineered wood floors – enhance comfort & sound insulation with the best options available!"Enhance your engineered wood floor with acoustic underlay for improved sound insulation and comfort.Enhance your flooring with acoustic wood floor underlay for improved soundproofing and comfort. Perfect for a quiet, stable base in any space."Choose the right underlay for solid wood flooring to enhance durability, comfort, and acoustics in your home.""Discover how wood flooring impacts acoustics: does it absorb sound or not? Learn the truth about its auditory effects in your space.""Enhance room acoustics with premium wood floor underlay, designed to reduce noise and provide superior sound insulation."Discover the benefits of using wood as a sturdy, reliable base for your laminate flooring, enhancing durability and performance.Enhance your floors with Woodtex laminate underlay for improved comfort, soundproofing, and durability. Ideal for a seamless flooring experience."Discover easy-to-install floating floors with built-in padding for superior comfort and noise reduction in your home or office.""Shop durable 12mm laminate flooring with a convenient pre-attached pad for easy installation and comfort.""Enhance your laminate flooring's durability with a 6 mil plastic barrier for moisture protection and stability. Perfect for longevity and upkeep.""Enhance your space with superior buildtec acoustics; choose premium laminate flooring insulation for soundproofing and comfort in every step."Maximize sound insulation with Buildtec Acoustics 2mm foam laminate underlay – the perfect base for quieter floors."Discover top laminate underlayments for second floors, enhancing comfort, durability & soundproofing in your upstairs spaces."Discover the top underlay options for basement laminate flooring to ensure durability, comfort, and moisture protection. Elevate your space today!"Discover top underlayment picks for laminate flooring in basements - enhance comfort, durability, and moisture protection.""Enhance your flooring with our 3mm foam laminate floor underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and noise reduction. Perfect support for any room!""Learn the quick steps to install cork underlayment for enhanced comfort & durability beneath your laminate flooring. Simple guide for a better floor base!"Learn to install laminate flooring with pre-attached pad quickly & easily for a seamless, sturdy finish in your home. Perfect DIY upgrade!"Quick guide on installing laminate flooring with pre-attached underlayment for a seamless, efficient home upgrade.""Enhance your laminate flooring with quality underlayment padding for better comfort, insulation, and noise reduction.""Shop top-quality laminate floor underlayment on Amazon. Enhance comfort & durability with perfect picks for your flooring!""Durable laminate flooring easily installs over carpet padding for a quick, stylish room makeover. Perfect for hassle-free updates!"Discover easy-install laminate flooring with built-in underlayment for a hassle-free, no extra layer needed upgrade to your space.High-quality laminate flooring with integrated underpad for easy installation and enhanced comfort. Durable, stylish & low-maintenance."Enhance your flooring with our laminate underlayment pad for improved comfort, noise reduction, and moisture protection. Perfect fit for your home!""Laminate with attached pad simplifies installation but may still require underlayment for optimal performance.""Laminate wood flooring with an attached pad offers easy installation and enhanced comfort in a durable, stylish finish."Install a vapor barrier before laying laminate flooring to protect against moisture and ensure long-lasting durability."Enhance your floors with Quick Step Real Sound Underlayment for superior sound reduction and moisture protection. Easy installation, immediate results!""Discover the ideal subflooring solutions for seamless laminate flooring installation and lasting performance.""Enhance your floors with quality timber laminate underlay for improved comfort, insulation, and durability. Perfect for a seamless finish."Maximize your floor's warmth and efficiency with our high-quality under-laminate insulation foil. Durable, easy to install, and energy-saving!"Enhance your vinyl flooring with quality underlayment for improved durability, comfort, and soundproofing. Perfect support for a flawless finish.""Enhance your laminate flooring with Buildtec underlayment for improved comfort, sound reduction, and moisture protection."Discover top picks for laminate floor padding that ensure comfort, durability, and improved acoustics in your home. Shop the best options now!"Discover the top moisture barriers for laminate flooring to protect & enhance your floors' durability and longevity. Ideal solutions for a dry surface!"Discover the top underlayments for floating floors on concrete to enhance durability, comfort, and soundproofing. Perfect fit for your flooring needs!Install moisture barrier underlayment to protect flooring from dampness - essential for a dry, long-lasting surface.Maximize flooring longevity with dual blue underlayment - superior moisture protection & sound reduction for a stable, quiet foundation."Durable floor padding designed to enhance laminate flooring: soundproof, comfortable & easy to install for long-lasting support.""Enhance your flooring with Lamilay underlay - superior comfort, durability, and sound insulation for laminate floors.""Ensure quiet steps with our laminate floor padding installation guide - a quick, easy way to enhance comfort and durability underfoot!""Find top-quality laminate flooring underlay options for builders. Durable, easy to install & enhances floor longevity. Shop now!""Discover durable laminate flooring with built-in vapor barrier for moisture protection. Ideal for a long-lasting, stylish home upgrade.""Explore durable, easy-to-install laminate flooring without pad for a sleek finish and direct surface feel in any room."">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/buildtecacoustics.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.u799090bfffcf63ee938900b8680023b2 p,.u799090bfffcf63ee938900b8680023b2 a,.u799090bfffcf63ee938900b8680023b2 span,.u799090bfffcf63ee938900b8680023b2 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.2px;
padding-right:8px;
padding-top:5.4px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.u799090bfffcf63ee938900b8680023b2 a,.x49292f86dd37593d4a2925a39f1f3738 a{
color:#0a0a0a!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
.x49292f86dd37593d4a2925a39f1f3738 p,.x49292f86dd37593d4a2925a39f1f3738 span,.x49292f86dd37593d4a2925a39f1f3738 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.u5d99b2adb2d67f99a3f428d75b59dc6e:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.3px 49.7px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.d26a99f7477501f5cb264790529aa4eed{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.2px 30.5px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.x49292f86dd37593d4a2925a39f1f3738 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.4px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
footer{
background:#050505;
color:#ffffff;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000!important;

}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
</style>
<script type="application/ld+json">

{
"@context":"https://schema.org",
"@type":"WebPage",
"headline":"best soundproof underlay for laminate flooring",
"url":"https://buildtecacoustics.co.uk/the-best-acoustic-underlay-on-the-market/",
"about":

[{"@type": "Thing", "name": "flooring", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=flooring&kgmid=/m/01c34b"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "underlay", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Underlay",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=underlay&kgmid=/m/05hh_z"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "floor", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Floor",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=floor&kgmid=/m/0l7_8"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "soundproofing", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=soundproofing&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "noise", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noise",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=noise&kgmid=/m/096lq0"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "laminate", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laminate_flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=laminate&kgmid=/m/04xvs0"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "foam", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Foam",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=foam&kgmid=/m/01nnqh"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "laminate flooring", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laminate_flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=laminate+flooring&kgmid=/m/04xvs0"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "subfloor", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Floor",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=subfloor&kgmid=/m/0l7_8"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "moisture", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moisture",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=moisture&kgmid=/m/02t59k"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "cork", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cork_(material)",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=cork&kgmid=/m/0k1ps"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "carpet", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carpet",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=carpet&kgmid=/m/01n5cy"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "rubber", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Natural_rubber",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=rubber&kgmid=/m/09kmv"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "acoustic", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acoustics",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=acoustic&kgmid=/m/0mx6"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "insulation", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=insulation&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "plywood", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plywood",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=plywood&kgmid=/m/0jh8w"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "vapor barrier", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vapor_barrier",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=vapor+barrier&kgmid=/m/0965r8"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "vinyl", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polyvinyl_chloride",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=vinyl&kgmid=/m/063js"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "concrete", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Concrete",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=concrete&kgmid=/m/01mxf"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "amazon", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amazon_(company)",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=amazon&kgmid=/m/0mgkg"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "noise reduction", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noise_reduction",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=noise+reduction&kgmid=/m/02f5h7"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "vibrations", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vibration",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=vibrations&kgmid=/m/01jwx6"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "soundproofing material", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=soundproofing+material&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "ceiling", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ceiling",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=ceiling&kgmid=/m/03gfsp"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "tape", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adhesive_tape",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=tape&kgmid=/m/03m3vtv"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "glue", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adhesive",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=glue&kgmid=/m/0z49"]}],

"mentions":

[{"@type": "Thing", "name": "r-value", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/R-value_(insulation)",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=r-value&kgmid=/m/01lncs"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "sound-blocking", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=sound-blocking&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "sound deadening", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=sound+deadening&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "sound transmission class", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sound_transmission_class",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=sound+transmission+class&kgmid=/m/0f5ct6"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "sound-insulation", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=sound-insulation&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "soundproofing materials", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=soundproofing+materials&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "sound-damping", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=sound-damping&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "soundproofed", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=soundproofed&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "floor covering", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=floor+covering&kgmid=/m/01c34b"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "insulation", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=insulation&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "floorboards", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=floorboards&kgmid=/m/01c34b"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "subfloors", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Floor",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=subfloors&kgmid=/m/0l7_8"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "acoustic foam", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soundproofing",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=acoustic+foam&kgmid=/m/01x_7_"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "noise reduction coefficient", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noise_reduction_coefficient",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=noise+reduction+coefficient&kgmid=/m/03cs3g"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "wetsuits", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wetsuit",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=wetsuits&kgmid=/m/01811m"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "curtains", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Curtain",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=curtains&kgmid=/m/03rszm"]},
{"@type": "Thing", "name": "flooring", "sameAs": ["https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flooring",
"https://www.google.com/search?q=flooring&kgmid=/m/01c34b"]}]
}

</script>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/buildtecacoustics.jpg" src="img/buildtecacoustics.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex ml-auto navbar-nav align-items-center"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="index.html" >soundproof underlay</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f nav-link" href="acoustic-underlay-for-laminate-floors.html" >acoustic underlay for laminate floors</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f nav-link" href="acoustic-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html" >acoustic underlay for laminate flooring</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="acoustic-underlay-for-laminate.html" >acoustic underlay for laminate</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f nav-link" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="best-acoustic-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >best acoustic underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-acoustic-underlay.html"  >laminate acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-acoustic-underlay-for-laminate.html"  >best acoustic underlay for laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="can-you-put-underlay-under-laminate-flooring.html"  >can you put underlay under laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-laminate.html"  >acoustic underlay laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-for-engineered-flooring.html"  >acoustic underlay for engineered flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-floor-acoustic-underlay.html"  >laminate floor acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="buildtec-acoustic-underlay.html"  >Buildtec acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="soundproof-underlay-for-laminate-flooring-uk.html"  >soundproof underlay for laminate flooring uk</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-soundproof-underlay-for-laminate-flooring-uk.html"  >best soundproof underlay for laminate flooring uk</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="what-thickness-underlay-is-best-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >what thickness underlay is best for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-acoustic-underlay-for-vinyl-flooring.html"  >best acoustic underlay for vinyl flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-for-vinyl-flooring.html"  >acoustic underlay for vinyl flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="vinyl-acoustic-underlay.html"  >vinyl acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-wood-floor.html"  >acoustic underlay wood floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-for-wooden-floors.html"  >acoustic underlay for wooden floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="3mm-acoustic-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >3mm acoustic underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="how-thick-should-underlay-be-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >how thick should underlay be for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="what-is-the-quietest-underlayment-for-laminate-floors.html"  >what is the quietest underlayment for laminate floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="3mm-acoustic-underlay.html"  >3mm acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="4mm-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >4mm underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-5mm.html"  >acoustic underlay 5mm</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="5mm-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >5mm underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="6mm-acoustic-underlay.html"  >6mm acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="6mm-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >6mm underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="6mm-laminate-underlay.html"  >6mm laminate underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="7mm-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >7mm underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="8mm-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >8mm underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="soundproof-underlay-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >soundproof underlay for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="soundproofing-underlay-for-vinyl.html"  >soundproofing underlay for vinyl</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="does-laminate-flooring-reduce-noise.html"  >does laminate flooring reduce noise</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="soundproofing-underlay-for-wooden-floors.html"  >soundproofing underlay for wooden floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="soundproof-wood-floor-underlay.html"  >soundproof wood floor underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-soundproof-underlay-for-wood-floors.html"  >best soundproof underlay for wood floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-soundproofing-underlayment-for-hardwood-floors.html"  >best soundproofing underlayment for hardwood floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="can-you-soundproof-a-wooden-floor.html"  >can you soundproof a wooden floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="how-do-you-soundproof-a-wooden-floor.html"  >how do you soundproof a wooden floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="can-you-soundproof-under-floorboards.html"  >can you soundproof under floorboards</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="how-to-soundproof-under-hardwood-floor.html"  >how to soundproof under hardwood floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="what-is-the-best-soundproofing-material-for-floors.html"  >what is the best soundproofing material for floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="wood-flooring-soundproof-underlay.html"  >wood flooring soundproof underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-for-solid-wood-flooring.html"  >acoustic underlay for solid wood flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="what-is-the-best-soundproofing-underlay.html"  >what is the best soundproofing underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="6mm-underlay-for-engineered-wood-flooring.html"  >6mm underlay for engineered wood flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="does-acoustic-underlay-work.html"  >does acoustic underlay work</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="is-acoustic-underlay-worth-it.html"  >is acoustic underlay worth it</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="do-you-put-underlay-under-wood-flooring.html"  >do you put underlay under wood flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="how-effective-is-acoustic-underlay.html"  >how effective is acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-acoustic-underlay-for-timber-floors.html"  >best acoustic underlay for timber floors</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="does-acoustic-underlay-make-a-difference.html"  >does acoustic underlay make a difference</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-acoustic-underlay-for-engineered-wood-floor.html"  >best acoustic underlay for engineered wood floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-underlay-for-engineered-wood-floor.html"  >acoustic underlay for engineered wood floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="acoustic-wood-floor-underlay.html"  >acoustic wood floor underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="what-underlay-for-solid-wood-flooring.html"  >what underlay for solid wood flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="does-wood-flooring-absorb-sound.html"  >does wood flooring absorb sound</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="wood-floor-acoustic-underlay.html"  >wood floor acoustic underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="wood-under-laminate-flooring.html"  >wood under laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="woodtex-laminate-underlay.html"  >woodtex laminate underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="floating-floor-with-padding.html"  >floating floor with padding</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="12mm-laminate-flooring-with-pad-attached.html"  >12mm laminate flooring with pad attached</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="6-mil-plastic-under-laminate-flooring.html"  >6 mil plastic under laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="buildte-acoustics-under-laminate-flooring-insulation.html"  >Buildte acoustics under laminate flooring insulation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="buildtec-acoustics-foam-laminate-underlay-2mm.html"  >Buildtec Acoustics foam laminate underlay 2mm</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-laminate-underlayment-for-second-floor.html"  >best laminate underlayment for second floor</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-underlay-for-basement-laminate.html"  >best underlay for basement laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-underlayment-for-laminate-flooring-in-basement.html"  >best underlayment for laminate flooring in basement</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="3mm-foam-laminate-floor-underlay.html"  >3mm foam laminate floor underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="installing-cork-underlayment-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >installing cork underlayment for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="installing-laminate-flooring-with-pad-attached.html"  >installing laminate flooring with pad attached</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="installing-laminate-flooring-with-underlayment-attached.html"  >installing laminate flooring with underlayment attached</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-floor-padding-underlayment.html"  >laminate floor padding underlayment</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-floor-underlayment-amazon.html"  >laminate floor underlayment amazon</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-on-carpet-pad.html"  >laminate flooring on carpet pad</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-that-doesn-t-require-underlayment.html"  >laminate flooring that doesn t require underlayment</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-with-underpad.html"  >laminate flooring with underpad</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-underlayment-pad.html"  >laminate underlayment pad</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-with-attached-pad-need-underlayment.html"  >laminate with attached pad need underlayment</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-wood-flooring-with-attached-pad.html"  >laminate wood flooring with attached pad</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laying-vapor-barrier-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >laying vapor barrier for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="quick-step-real-sound-underlayment.html"  >quick step real sound underlayment</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="sub-flooring-for-laminate.html"  >sub flooring for laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="timber-laminate-flooring-underlay.html"  >timber laminate flooring underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="under-laminate-floor-insulation-foil.html"  >under laminate floor insulation foil</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="under-laminate-for-vinyl-flooring.html"  >under laminate for vinyl flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="buildtec-underlayment-for-laminate.html"  >Buildtec underlayment for laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-laminate-floor-padding.html"  >best laminate floor padding</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-moisture-barrier-for-laminate-flooring.html"  >best moisture barrier for laminate flooring</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="best-underlayment-for-floating-floor-on-concrete.html"  >best underlayment for floating floor on concrete</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="moisture-barrier-underlayment-installation.html"  >moisture barrier underlayment installation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="dual-blue-underlayment.html"  >dual blue underlayment</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="floor-padding-for-under-laminate.html"  >floor padding for under laminate</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="lamilay-underlay.html"  >lamilay underlay</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-floor-padding-installation.html"  >laminate floor padding installation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-underlay-builders.html"  >laminate flooring underlay builders</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-with-vapor-barrier.html"  >laminate flooring with vapor barrier</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="laminate-flooring-without-pad.html"  >laminate flooring without pad</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="btn btn-md d26a99f7477501f5cb264790529aa4eed" href="https://buildtecacoustics.co.uk/contact-us/" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Buildtec Acoustics</h1>
<p>At Buildtec Acoustics one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Buildtec Acoustics and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: buildtecacoustics.co.uk</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Buildtec Acoustics. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Buildtec Acoustics, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Buildtec Acoustics follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Buildtec Acoustics.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Buildtec Acoustics, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Buildtec Acoustics has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Buildtec Acoustics's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Buildtec Acoustics does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Buildtec Acoustics</br>
07553 473877</br>
2 Loughgall Road, Armagh Business Centre 	</br>
</br>
Co. Armagh</br>
buildtecacoustics.co.uk</br>
info@buildtecacoustics.co.uk</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 container pt-5" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>Buildtec Acoustics</p>
<p>Phone : 07553 473877</p>
<p>Email : info@buildtecacoustics.co.uk</p>
<p>State : Co. Armagh</p>
<p>Zip : BT61 7NH</p>
<p>Address : 2 Loughgall Road, Armagh Business Centre 	</p>
<p><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="https://www.google.com/search?q=Buildtec+Acoustics&stick=H4sIAAAAAAAA_-NgU1I1qEg0N0lLTjQ1TkozMTZJNjK2MqgwNDQxtExJMrMwTEuxNDczWMQq5FSamZNSkpqs4JicX1pckplcDAA5lIENPgAAAA&hl=en&mat=CWdrzgDKiFKVElcB7PxHsXey22LGOCt5fsF0soXCNO_fssiXgo6TV5y7-CvNVyQetwJHxqOyM3Pi0MICzKCe0GHgCk6ZSbuZuD-GBlzNMasbOv2ix1w2_xm9w21EtDzshZk&authuser=0" rel="nofollow"> Google Business Profile</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="buildtecacoustics.co.uk" rel="nofollow">buildtecacoustics.co.uk</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>USEFUL LINKS</p>
<p><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="https://acousticunderlay.sos-ch-dk-2.exo.io/laminate/index.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Laminage acoustic underlay</a></p></div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="ub941232e9cbfffe377949e27691a361f" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
